[
  {
    "question": "2 + 5",
    "correctAnswer": 7,
    "choices": [
      9,
      6,
      8,
      7
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 + 4",
    "correctAnswer": 7,
    "choices": [
      5,
      7,
      6,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 2",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "choices": [
      4,
      3,
      5,
      2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "34 + 49",
    "correctAnswer": 83,
    "choices": [
      82,
      81,
      80,
      83
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "47 + 48",
    "correctAnswer": 95,
    "choices": [
      95,
      92,
      96,
      93
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 + 34",
    "correctAnswer": 64,
    "choices": [
      67,
      62,
      63,
      64
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "32 + 50",
    "correctAnswer": 82,
    "choices": [
      84,
      85,
      82,
      81
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "43 + 48",
    "correctAnswer": 91,
    "choices": [
      91,
      93,
      94,
      90
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "37 + 29",
    "correctAnswer": 66,
    "choices": [
      65,
      63,
      67,
      66
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 + 14",
    "correctAnswer": 44,
    "choices": [
      43,
      45,
      44,
      41
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "39 + 38",
    "correctAnswer": 77,
    "choices": [
      78,
      80,
      77,
      79
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "36 + 18",
    "correctAnswer": 54,
    "choices": [
      53,
      55,
      54,
      51
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 + 14",
    "correctAnswer": 21,
    "choices": [
      21,
      18,
      23,
      24
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "45 + 30",
    "correctAnswer": 75,
    "choices": [
      78,
      75,
      72,
      73
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 + 11",
    "correctAnswer": 16,
    "choices": [
      13,
      17,
      16,
      14
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 + 23",
    "correctAnswer": 38,
    "choices": [
      38,
      39,
      36,
      37
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 + 6",
    "correctAnswer": 26,
    "choices": [
      26,
      29,
      28,
      23
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 + 34",
    "correctAnswer": 44,
    "choices": [
      45,
      43,
      46,
      44
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "21 + 8",
    "correctAnswer": 29,
    "choices": [
      29,
      32,
      26,
      28
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 + 3",
    "correctAnswer": 10,
    "choices": [
      7,
      13,
      8,
      10
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "24 + 49",
    "correctAnswer": 73,
    "choices": [
      71,
      73,
      76,
      74
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "41 + 19",
    "correctAnswer": 60,
    "choices": [
      61,
      60,
      58,
      62
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "47 + 16",
    "correctAnswer": 63,
    "choices": [
      60,
      63,
      61,
      64
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "32 + 12",
    "correctAnswer": 44,
    "choices": [
      44,
      41,
      46,
      45
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 + 23",
    "correctAnswer": 41,
    "choices": [
      41,
      43,
      42,
      38
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 23",
    "correctAnswer": 42,
    "choices": [
      39,
      41,
      44,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "33 + 8",
    "correctAnswer": 41,
    "choices": [
      44,
      41,
      40,
      43
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 + 22",
    "correctAnswer": 31,
    "choices": [
      28,
      30,
      29,
      31
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 + 27",
    "correctAnswer": 57,
    "choices": [
      54,
      59,
      56,
      57
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "48 + 37",
    "correctAnswer": 85,
    "choices": [
      85,
      82,
      84,
      87
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "43 + 20",
    "correctAnswer": 63,
    "choices": [
      63,
      65,
      60,
      62
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "23 + 40",
    "correctAnswer": 63,
    "choices": [
      63,
      65,
      66,
      60
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 + 3",
    "correctAnswer": 10,
    "choices": [
      10,
      12,
      9,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 + 40",
    "correctAnswer": 43,
    "choices": [
      42,
      43,
      40,
      45
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "40 + 11",
    "correctAnswer": 51,
    "choices": [
      53,
      51,
      52,
      48
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 + 29",
    "correctAnswer": 43,
    "choices": [
      42,
      44,
      43,
      41
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 + 36",
    "correctAnswer": 49,
    "choices": [
      49,
      47,
      50,
      51
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 + 17",
    "correctAnswer": 29,
    "choices": [
      32,
      26,
      27,
      29
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 + 47",
    "correctAnswer": 60,
    "choices": [
      61,
      60,
      59,
      62
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "11 + 44",
    "correctAnswer": 55,
    "choices": [
      53,
      55,
      57,
      56
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "36 + 46",
    "correctAnswer": 82,
    "choices": [
      84,
      85,
      82,
      79
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "40 + 34",
    "correctAnswer": 74,
    "choices": [
      74,
      75,
      73,
      77
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "33 + 48",
    "correctAnswer": 81,
    "choices": [
      79,
      81,
      82,
      78
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "32 + 43",
    "correctAnswer": 75,
    "choices": [
      76,
      77,
      75,
      73
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "38 + 32",
    "correctAnswer": 70,
    "choices": [
      67,
      70,
      73,
      69
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 + 44",
    "correctAnswer": 50,
    "choices": [
      47,
      51,
      49,
      50
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "21 + 15",
    "correctAnswer": 36,
    "choices": [
      39,
      35,
      33,
      36
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "29 + 4",
    "correctAnswer": 33,
    "choices": [
      35,
      33,
      30,
      34
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 19",
    "correctAnswer": 21,
    "choices": [
      23,
      19,
      20,
      21
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "46 + 46",
    "correctAnswer": 92,
    "choices": [
      89,
      91,
      92,
      90
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 + 15",
    "correctAnswer": 35,
    "choices": [
      37,
      35,
      33,
      34
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "28 + 46",
    "correctAnswer": 74,
    "choices": [
      72,
      77,
      73,
      74
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 + 32",
    "correctAnswer": 39,
    "choices": [
      39,
      37,
      38,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "36 + 3",
    "correctAnswer": 39,
    "choices": [
      41,
      40,
      39,
      36
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 + 7",
    "correctAnswer": 17,
    "choices": [
      20,
      14,
      18,
      17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 + 50",
    "correctAnswer": 55,
    "choices": [
      56,
      52,
      57,
      55
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 + 21",
    "correctAnswer": 31,
    "choices": [
      34,
      32,
      31,
      33
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "35 + 10",
    "correctAnswer": 45,
    "choices": [
      46,
      42,
      45,
      48
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 + 29",
    "correctAnswer": 41,
    "choices": [
      41,
      38,
      40,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "25 + 31",
    "correctAnswer": 56,
    "choices": [
      58,
      54,
      56,
      59
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 32",
    "correctAnswer": 51,
    "choices": [
      54,
      48,
      51,
      49
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 + 36",
    "correctAnswer": 43,
    "choices": [
      44,
      43,
      46,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 11",
    "correctAnswer": 30,
    "choices": [
      29,
      30,
      33,
      28
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 46",
    "correctAnswer": 48,
    "choices": [
      49,
      51,
      48,
      50
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "21 + 44",
    "correctAnswer": 65,
    "choices": [
      65,
      64,
      62,
      67
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "37 + 1",
    "correctAnswer": 38,
    "choices": [
      38,
      41,
      40,
      37
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "7 + 24",
    "correctAnswer": 31,
    "choices": [
      31,
      30,
      28,
      33
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 + 15",
    "correctAnswer": 28,
    "choices": [
      26,
      27,
      28,
      30
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "34 + 48",
    "correctAnswer": 82,
    "choices": [
      82,
      83,
      85,
      80
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "5 + 29",
    "correctAnswer": 34,
    "choices": [
      37,
      35,
      36,
      34
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 + 34",
    "correctAnswer": 46,
    "choices": [
      43,
      45,
      47,
      46
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "38 + 12",
    "correctAnswer": 50,
    "choices": [
      52,
      50,
      47,
      51
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 + 18",
    "correctAnswer": 34,
    "choices": [
      35,
      32,
      34,
      36
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "41 + 16",
    "correctAnswer": 57,
    "choices": [
      57,
      55,
      59,
      60
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 + 41",
    "correctAnswer": 50,
    "choices": [
      51,
      52,
      50,
      49
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "47 + 15",
    "correctAnswer": 62,
    "choices": [
      62,
      59,
      65,
      61
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "34 + 6",
    "correctAnswer": 40,
    "choices": [
      38,
      43,
      39,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "9 + 40",
    "correctAnswer": 49,
    "choices": [
      50,
      48,
      51,
      49
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "24 + 38",
    "correctAnswer": 62,
    "choices": [
      64,
      60,
      62,
      59
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "32 + 35",
    "correctAnswer": 67,
    "choices": [
      65,
      64,
      69,
      67
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 + 22",
    "correctAnswer": 52,
    "choices": [
      49,
      51,
      52,
      53
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "22 + 38",
    "correctAnswer": 60,
    "choices": [
      63,
      59,
      57,
      60
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 + 46",
    "correctAnswer": 60,
    "choices": [
      60,
      62,
      63,
      59
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 + 36",
    "correctAnswer": 66,
    "choices": [
      68,
      66,
      65,
      64
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "26 + 43",
    "correctAnswer": 69,
    "choices": [
      69,
      68,
      71,
      70
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "6 + 9",
    "correctAnswer": 15,
    "choices": [
      17,
      14,
      18,
      15
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 + 7",
    "correctAnswer": 23,
    "choices": [
      23,
      25,
      20,
      26
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "24 + 35",
    "correctAnswer": 59,
    "choices": [
      61,
      59,
      56,
      62
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 + 6",
    "correctAnswer": 20,
    "choices": [
      21,
      17,
      20,
      23
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 + 38",
    "correctAnswer": 54,
    "choices": [
      55,
      54,
      51,
      56
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "42 + 27",
    "correctAnswer": 69,
    "choices": [
      69,
      68,
      72,
      66
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "41 + 35",
    "correctAnswer": 76,
    "choices": [
      78,
      76,
      79,
      77
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 + 25",
    "correctAnswer": 40,
    "choices": [
      42,
      41,
      39,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "37 + 32",
    "correctAnswer": 69,
    "choices": [
      69,
      66,
      70,
      68
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "29 + 17",
    "correctAnswer": 46,
    "choices": [
      44,
      43,
      45,
      46
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "26 + 27",
    "correctAnswer": 53,
    "choices": [
      52,
      54,
      53,
      50
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "3 + 45",
    "correctAnswer": 48,
    "choices": [
      47,
      48,
      49,
      50
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "27 + 11",
    "correctAnswer": 38,
    "choices": [
      36,
      41,
      39,
      38
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "4 + 17",
    "correctAnswer": 21,
    "choices": [
      21,
      23,
      19,
      24
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 + 14",
    "correctAnswer": 26,
    "choices": [
      26,
      28,
      24,
      23
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 + 36",
    "correctAnswer": 51,
    "choices": [
      54,
      48,
      49,
      51
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "39 + 14",
    "correctAnswer": 53,
    "choices": [
      53,
      51,
      54,
      56
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "16 + 40",
    "correctAnswer": 56,
    "choices": [
      59,
      54,
      56,
      58
    ]
  }
]